

Hailing from the city of Indore and working towards building a successful and meaningful practice in the corporate world, I'm eager for opportunities to contribute practically with my theoretical knowledge, as well as to expand it.

I am keen to explore the many disciplines in the field of management and am therefore, presently working with two organizations with diverse roles and responsibilities. I am also working on a research paper on consumer psychology and behaviour, 'Add to cart or Buy now'.

Enthusiastic and driven, I enjoy positions of responsibility and opportunities for community welfare. Going ahead, I am excited to contribute to businesses with my reasoning and networking skills.

CONTACT

advikajainz@gmail.com +91 9098555295

http://linkedin.com/in/advika-jain-657968198

ADVIKA JAIN

WORK EXPERIENCE

 Fundraising and marketing intern, Youth Empowerment Foundation, India April 2020 - present

Creating, managing and running a fundraising campaign to support daily wagers affected by the COVID -19 pandemic.

• Digital marketing intern, CityFurnish

March 2020 - present

Contributed to increased reach by managing CityFurnish's numerous social media profiles. Prepared weekly updates and reports to track success rates of marketing campaigns.

EDUCATION

ВВА,	Marketing and Finance	Symbiosis Centre for Management Studies, Pune	-	2019 ~
Class (CBSI		Sri Sathya Sai Vidya Vihar, Indore	84.6%	2018 - 2019
Class (CBSI		Sri Sathya Sai Vidya Vihar, Indore	9.4 GPA	2016 - 2017

ROLES OF RESPONSIBILITY

SCMS	Core member, Hospitality Department, Sympulse Headed the back-office team, overviewing accommodation and transport operations	2019-20
	Core member, Entrepreneurship cell Conducted various events, social media campaigns and workshops collaborating with B-schools across the country	2019-20
SSSVV	Head, Cultural committee Headed a team of 12+ students in the organization of all school events	2016-18
	Core member, Organizing Committee, SAIMUN Co-ordinated complete participation and logistics of 200+ delegates	2019-20

SOCIAL ENGAGEMENT

• Bhumi

April 2020 - present

Data interpretation for distribution of resources for Bhumi's food drive

• Teaching Volunteer, Bloom

February 2020 - present

Held classroom sessions with young underpriviledged girls on untouched and taboo topics like menstrual health, the female body and touch.

RESEARCH AND PAPER PRESENTATIONS

• Wrote a research paper on consumer behaviour and psychology, titled 'Add to cart or Buy now'.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Avid participation in *public speaking* activities Anchored various school events and represented the school in several inter-school competitions.
- UNEP Delegate at IIMUN, 2017